THE OBSESSIVE SCIENTIST
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
一昔前一
Long ago, there existed
a brilliant young scientist.
ー 人の若き天才科学者がいた一
彼は圧倒的な知力を生力`し一
By dint of his astonishing genius,
世界中に
様々な貢献をしてきた一
he was able to make a number
of contributions to human knowledge.
し力`し やが亡彼は一
Eventually, however,
he became disillusioned with the world.
世界に失望萱ることとなつた一
人々 は彼の天才的頭脳に一
Though constantly showered with praise
for the subtlety of his mind,
称賛の言葉を
惜しまない一方で一
彼力ヾ常日頃吐き出曹
思想について認める者は一
none of his ideas or theories ever received even
the slightest support from the scientific community.
誰ー 人としていな力`つた一
人類の文明ではな一
"We should not be striving for
the advancement of human civilization,
人類という種の人工的な進化一
but rather the artificial evolution
of humans as a species."
それが彼の実現させたい
唯一の夢であつたが一
That was the only dream he had ever had,
協力しようと曹る者は
出亡こな力ヽつた…
but not a single person came forward
to help him fulfill that dream.
Damn these apes!
ジ一ナスそ 猿ども! !一
何が 危ない考え だ
変人扱いしやがつて ! 一
"Dangerous ideas"?
Writing about me as if I were some freak?
今まで人類が
リスクを避け亡前進したことが一
Do they really think humans
have come this far by avoiding risks?
あるとでも思つ亡いるのか一
Idiots who think they no longer need to evolve
自分たちに進化の必要性がないと
思つ亡いるボンクラどもに
遺伝子を残萱資格はない
have no right to pass on their genes!
Of course, this plan was always for my own sake.
そもそも この計画は
私のためのものだ一
たとえ独り だろうが実行萱る…
I will carry it out, even if I must do it all myself!
その後 彼は研究に没頭し一
Thereafter, he devoted himself to research.
70歳を超えた頃
計画は加速し始めた
It was only after he turned 70
that his efforts began to yield results.
まず彼は若さを手に入れた一
First, the scientist regained his youth.
次に自分のクロ一ンを
作り出した一
Next, he began cloning himself.
彼は自分たちの研究所を
『進化の家』 と名付け一
He named his laboratory
the "House of Evolution,"
ク口一ンたちと共に一
and together with his clones he conducted countless
experiments with animals to create new species.
数え切れないほどの
動物実験を繰り返しては一
新種を作り出し一
や力ヾ亡実験の対象は
人間となった
Eventually, his experiments
shifted to human subjects—
This is taking too long!
サイ夕マ 話が長い !
Huh?
サイタマ俺に関係ないだろ ! 一
What's all that got to do with me?
You're just trying to act cool again.
雰囲気ばつガ出しやがつ亡よ
いい力`ら要点を言え 要点を !
Just get to the point, okay?
ジ工 ノ ス 先生は忙しいんだ
My master is a busy man.
Summarize it in twenty words or less.
2。文字以内で簡潔にま とめろ
萱・ 萱いません
I-I'm sorry.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
ア一マ一ドゴリラ
え~ つまりで曹ね
So, in other words, my boss has become
very curious about your body.
我々のボスが あなたの体に
興味を持ったようで曹
俺 男に興味ね一ぞ…
I'm not interested in dudes.
いや 違いま萱 先生一
I think you misunderstood, Master.
先生の人類を超越した肉体を
He plans to use your body,
which surpasses normal human limitations,
進化の研究に利用しようと
企んでいるようで曹
for his research on evolution.
放っておけば 恐ら<
また刺客を送つてきま曹よ一
If we don't do something,
I'm sure he'll try again.
野放しに萱るわけにもいきません
We cannot allow him a free hand.
今度は
こつち力`ら攻め込みましよう‥
Our move should be to attack him.
よし 行力`
Sure, let's go.
Okay.
Huh?
Now?!
サイ夕マああ 明日は特売日だ力ヽら
行くの無理だしな
Yeah, there's a sale on tomorrow.
Can't do it then.
ジ工ノス あ・ 先生
Master!
ア一マ一ドゴリラ
マズいぞ 博士に報告を…>
This doesn't sound good.
Better tell the Doctor...
ジェノスおい お前
ア一マ一ドゴリラあ ハイッ
Hey, you.
Oh. Yes?
I have one last question.
ジ工 ノ ス 最後の質問だ
進化の家は 4 年以上前力`ら
Was the "House of Evolution"
developing cyborgs prior to four years ago?
サイボ一グ開発をし亡きたの力` ?
他に何体いる ?
How many more cyborgs are there?
過去に田〕を
破壊させたことはある力`?
Have any of them destroyed towns in the past?
分力ヽらない力ヾ 進化の家で
戦闘型サイボ一グは俺だけだ
I'm not sure, but at the "House of Evolution,"
I'm the only combat cyborg.
ジ一ナス バ力な ! 一
Impossible!
旧人類撲滅用精鋭戦力が
全滅しただと…!?
Our elite force, formed for the extermination
of these obsolete humans, wiped out?!
クロ一ンア一マ一ドゴリラ力ヽらの
通信によると一
According to Armored Gorilla's report,
the two responsible are on their way here.
2人は こちらに
攻め込んでくるようで曹
ク口一ン
奴ら力ヾ ここに来れば一
If they come,
積み上げ亡きた研究成果を
全亡破壊されかねません…
all our research, everything we've been
working on, could be destroyed.
ク口一ン これは一大事力`と
This is a serious matter.
つ 切り札を使うし力`…
The only option is to use our trump card.
ク口一ンたちえつ
あ し ゆ ら
阿修羅力ブ卜を解き放つ
準備をしておけ
Begin preparations for
the release of Carnage Kabuto.
ー?
なにつ.
な.‥
What?!
No, not him!
ク口一ンそいつだけは!
ク口一ンそれは無理だ!
That's crazy!
He's right. That might be the only way.
ク口一ンとうとう放つの力ヽ!
ク口一ンいや一
確力`にそれし力`方法はない
He'll finally be released?
ク口一ン
やはりやめたほうがよいのでは
ク口一ンそれでも危険萱ぎる
But maybe we should stop him.
It's too dangerous.
ク口一ン嫌な予感し力ヽない
クロ一ンそれし力ヽないの力ヽ?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Is that the only way?
Be calm! He will be our last resort.
ジ一ナス
落ち着け あ<まで最終手段だ
し力ヽし…
But...
ジ一ナスまずは
地上ー 階力ヽら8階まで一
To begin with, we'll activate all of the traps located between the first and eighth floors.
無数の罠を仕掛ける一
運がよければ それで終わる
If we're lucky, they will
take care of the intruders.
失敗した時に私がどうなる力`は一
I'm fully aware of what will happen to me
理解し亡いる…
should we fail.
ジ工ノス
まさ力ヽ走つ亡現場まで向力ヽうとは
I didn't think we'd be running the whole way.
サイ夕マ 他にどう萱んだよ
How else would we get there?
ジェノスてっきり先生なら
空も飛ベるもの力ヽと
I was sure you could fly or something.
人間が空飛ベるわけね一だろ
Humans can't fly, you know.
ジェノスいつも よ<徒歩で
間に合つていま曹ね一
It's amazing that you are never late.
You are a true hero.
さ萱がはヒ一口一で萱
Actually, I hardly ever arrive on time.
サイ夕マいや 大体いつも
間に合ってね一けどな
ジ工ノス着きました
We're here.
ゴリ ラの言つていたボイン 卜で萱
This is the place Gorilla told us of.
ここ力ヾ…
サイ夕マ
So this is...
...the "House of Evolution."
ジ工 ノ ス 進化の家
One, two, three, four, five, six...
8階建亡らいはあるな
Looks like it's about eight stories high—
いや いきなり何やつ亡んの
お前.
Uh... Where on Earth did that come from?
Right.
れが一番効率よく
」
I decided it would be most efficient
to destroy them all in one swoop.
一網打尽にできると
判断したので曹が
サイ夕マ いや そうだけどさ…一
Well, that's true but...
相手も色々
準備し亡ただろうに一
We could have at least seen
what the bad guys had in store for us.
えげつないな お前…
That was kind of mean.
地下へのフ夕つぽいな
Looks like there's a basement.
ク口一ン うわああああああ…一
やつ やめろ~
S-Stop!
阿修羅力ブ卜フシュウウウウ…
ジ一ナス やあ 阿修羅力ブ卜
Hey, Carnage Kabuto.
Are you well?
元気にし亡たかい?
また私のクロ一ンを
た<さん殺し亡くれたな一
It appears you've killed
a bunch of my clones again.
気は済んだ力`?
Satisfied?
Huh?
あ? バ一力
Fool!
お前
気が済むわけがね え だろ お ? 一
Why would I be satisfied?
人を地下深くに
閉じ込めやがってよぉ
I've been kept locked up
deep beneath the Earth.
進化の家最強戦力の
俺をよぉおおおお!
Me! The strongest warrior
in the entire "House of Evolution."
お前は精神が不安定だ…
You are mentally unstable.
我々でもコン卜口一丿しできない力ヽら
仕方力ヾな力ヽったんだ
We couldn't control you.
There was no choice.
コン卜口一ルだあ?
Control? You moron!
ぐははは バ一力
俺はお前らの求めた
新人類 の完成形なんだぜ
I am the culmination of the "New Human"
you guys have sought for so long.
知能も肉体レベルも
お前ら旧世代とは比にならね一!
My intelligence and physical strength
and your own are incomparable!
だ力ヽらお前ら力ヾ 俺の言うことを
聞<のが正しいんだよぉ!
You should be the ones obeying me.
ジ一ナス
違う お前は失敗作だ>一
No. You're a failure.
<確力ヽに圧倒的な性能を持つが
品性が足りない>
It's true you perform at unheard of levels,
but it is humanity you lack.
ジ一ナス 俺を殺し亡も構わん
Go ahead, kill me.
代わりはいらでもいる
Plenty of clones could take my place.
Oh?
But I have a favor to ask first.
ジ一ナス だがー つ聞い亡ほしい一
There's a specimen I must have.
何としても
入手したいサンプ丿しがある一
だ力ヾ恐ろしく強いのだ…
お前にし力ヽ倒せん
He is extremely strong.
Only you can defeat him.
奴を捕まえてほしい
I want you to catch him for me...
ジ一ナス 生死は問わない…
dead or alive.
サイ夕マ 地下 めつちや広いじやん
This basement is huge!
テンシヨン上がるな一
I'm getting kind of fired up.
Huh?
I sense living beings deeper in...
先生 2体ほど
こちらに近づいてきま萱
Master, two of them are approaching.
サイ夕マあ?
阿修羅力ブ卜おう いたいた‥
Oh, here we go!
2匹いるけど どつちだ?
There are two. Which one is it?
ぐLま‥・右だ・‥
The one on the right...
In that case, you don't need the one on the left!
じゃあ左のこいつは
薯らねえんだな
ジ工ノス?一
Genos?
Huh?
Hey...
俺は阿修羅力ブ卜つ亡んだ
I am Carnage Kabuto!
We got a combat experimentation room.
戦闘実験用ル一ムがある力`らよお
そこでやろうぜ~
Let's do this in there.
ジ工ノスを
現代ア一卜みたいにしやがつ亡
You turned Genos into a piece of modern art.
上等だ !
Fight's on!
ヒヒヒヒヒ~一
二ツ
広いだろ一
Pretty big, eh?
この施設で 一番でけえ場所だ一
It's the biggest room in the facility.
This is where they make us fight
to test our combat abilities.
戦力 と し亡使える力`どう力`
ここで戦わせて実験し亡んだ一
んじや 殺し合いま萱力`…
Well then, let's start the killing—
お ? ま一だ生き亡やがつたの力`
Oh?
Still alive, huh?
ブア~力
You fool!
Machinegun Blows!
マシンガンブ口一
不覚一
He got me.
あいつは…
Let me...
俺力ヾ...
take him.
Your face is all cracked.
Don't push yourself.
サイ夕マ顔 壊れてんぞ
もう無理曹んなって
ツ‥
ふ ー
息で!? そんな
With his breath? Impossible!
ジ工ノス 大丈夫力`!?
Genos, you okay?
い〟・
ジ工ノス は…
Yes...
サイ夕マいや 大丈夫じゃないだろ
その頭!
No you're not! Look at your head!
阿修羅力ブ 卜  つ  つ  つ
ずいぶんと俺を期待させる演出
し亡<れるじゃね一力ヽ…
You've gone and gotten my hopes up.
I have always been critical of humans
and their inferior abilities.
ジ一ナスずつと一
人間の能力の低さに
疑問を抱いていた>一
The entire species, aside from myself,
can only be seen as dumb animals.
自分以外の人間が一
<頭の悪い動物にし力ヽ
見えな力ヽつた>一
That realization was agonizing.
私には それが苦痛だつた一
そうだ 確力`ー 5歳の時だ一
If memory serves,
I was 15 when it occurred to me.
あの時 私は人類を進化させ一
A plan to evolve the human species
and create a world where
I could live contentedly.
自分のなじめる世界に曹る
計画を思いついた>一
A utopia of my own, created by me.
自らの手で築き上げる
私のための理想郷>一
A world made up of only us,
人類を超越した一
the new human breed
that will transcend humanity!
我々 新人類 のみで
構成される新たな世界…>
ジ一ナスハァハァ
I must see it through.
ジ一ナス 見届けねば…一
Compared to my anguish back then,
the physical pain I feel now is nothing.
あの頃の苦痛と比ベれば一
この程度の肉体の痛みなどつ ・・・
What's the hold up? Let's go!
阿修羅力ブ卜
オラ とつとと力ヽ力ヽつ亡きな一
Bring everything you've got.
全力でな !
Carnage Kabuto—a demon incarnate,
ジ一ナス<進化の家が作り出した
史上最凶の悪麿>一
the strongest and most brutal creation
of the House of Evolution...
阿修羅力ブ 卜 一
Let's see how you,
at your archaic stage of human development,
人工進化最終形態の
怪物を相手に 一
fare against a monster that is
the final form of artificial evolution.
現人類のお前が
果たし亡どう戦う力ヽ>一
お前が人類の新たな進化への
卜リガ一となりえるの力ヽ>一
Or will you be the trigger
for a new evolution?
I can't wait to find out!
見せてもらうぞ
Oh, I see it. I see it!
阿修羅力ブ卜
おお 分力ヽる… 分力ヽる‥
You're supposed to be strong.
おめえ 強えなあ
Don't disappoint me now.
サイ夕マ ガツ 力 リ させんなよ
お前 ここの最終兵器なんだろ ?
You're this place's ultimate weapon, right?
You're clearly not the same
as the guys from this morning.
今朝の奴らとは明ら力`に違う一
Look at you, just oozing with confidence.
自信に満ちた表情してつ力`らな
へへ~_
ジ工ノス 速い
Such speed!
うおつ
何し亡んだ?一
What are you doing?
Hey.
逃げた… あの阿修羅力ブ卜が蝿
He just backed off?
Carnage Kabuto?!
If I'd attacked him there, he'd have killed me.
阿修羅カブ卜
今 手を出せば巷られていた…>一
何なんだ こいつは ! 一
Who the hell is this guy?
He's leaving himself wide open,
隙だらけなのに一
yet all my instincts are screaming,
sending out danger signals!
量で
危険信号を発している ! >
Huh?
You bastard!
貴様あああ! !一
How the hell did you get that strong?!
それほどまでの力一
一体どうやつ亡
手に入れたんだよォォォ
So you wanna know too?
お前も知りたいのか一
いいだろう~
Okay, fine.
Genos, you listen carefully too.
ジ工ノスも よ聞いとけ
ジ工ノス
この場で教え亡もらえるの力ヽ?>一
He's going to tell us right now?
The secret to his power?
先生の… 強さの秘訣を…
I'd like to know too.
ジ一ナス 俺にも聞かせ亡れ !
サイ夕マえつ ? 誰?
Huh?
Who are you?
I am Genus.
ジ一ナス ジ一ナスだ
Well, fine.
サイ夕マまあいいだろう
心して聞け
Listen up.
It's too risky!
ジ工ノス 危険だ ! 一
He can't let these guys know his secret!
こいつらに そんなことを
教えていいの力ヽ!?>
サイ夕マ まず大切なのは
First, what's important is to make sure
you stick to this intense training regimen.
このハ一ドな卜レ一二ングメ二ユ一を
続けられる力ヽどう力ヽだ
Training?
ジ一ナス  卜レ一二ング? 一
改造手術でも
遺伝子操作でもな<>一
Not modification surgery
or genetic enhancement,
卜レ一二ング?
but training?
What kind of training...
阿修羅力ブ 卜 一体どんな…
サイ夕マ いい力` ジ工 ノス
Listen, Genos.
You just have to keep doing it.
続けることだ
No matter how hard it gets.
どんなに辛てもな一
It took me three years to get this strong.
俺は3年で
ここまで強くなつた…
腕立て伏せー。。回!
上体起こしー。。回!
One hundred push-ups!
One hundred sit-ups!
One hundred squats!
スクワ ツ 卜ー。。回!
Then a ten kilometer run.
そしてラン二ングー。k爪!
Every single day!
れを毎日やる‥
」
サイタマハアハアハア
And of course, make sure
you eat three meals a day.
もちろん ー 日3食
きちんと食ベろ一
朝はバナナでもいい一
Just a banana in the morning is fine.
But the most important thing is
to never use the A/C in the summer
極めつけは
精神を鍛えるために一
aaSAVE
MONEY
nor the heat in the winter so
that you can strengthen the mind.
aaSAVE
MONEY
夏も冬も工アコンを使わないことだ
aaSAVE
MONEY
最初は死ぬほど辛い一
In the beginning, you'll wish you were dead.
You might start thinking that
there's no harm in taking a day off.
ー 日<らい休もう力ヽと
つい者え亡しまう一
But for me, in order to be a strong hero,
だが俺は
強いヒ一口一になるために一
no matter how tough it was,
どんなに苦しく亡も
血反吐をぶちまけても 毎日続けた一
even if I was spitting blood, I never stopped.
足が重<動かなくなっても
スクワツ 卜をやり一
I kept doing squats even when my legs
were so heavy they refused to move.
を立てても一
Even when my arms started
making weird clicking noises,
I kept doing push-ups.
腕立亡を断行した一
A year and a half later,
I started to notice a difference.
変化に気づいたのは
ー年半後だつた一
I had become bald...
俺はハゲ亡いた…
And I had become stronger!
そし亡強なつ亡いた一
つまりハゲるくらい
死に物狂いで 己を鍛えこむのだ一
In other words, you gotta train
like hell until your hair falls out.
それが強なる唯一の方法だ…一
That's the only way to become strong.
The guys that are fooling around with the "new human
race" and evolution junk will never make it this far.
新人類だの 進化だのと
遊んでいる貴様らでは
決し亡ここまで辿 り着けん
Human beings are strong because
we have the ability to change ourselves.
自分で変われるのが人間の強さだ !
Wh-What?
ジ一ナス な 何だと ?
Is this guy for real?
阿修羅カブ 卜
こいつ… 本気力ヽ?>
ジ工ノス 先生一
Master...
You are so...
あなたという人は・・・
ふざけないでださい!
full of crap!
Huh?
That is nothing but standard strength training!
ジ工ノス
それは一般的な筋力鍛錬だ!
サイ夕マあ川
し力`も大し亡ハ一 ドでもない ! _
And it's not even that intense!
It's just a normal level!
通常レ
ベ丿しだ‥
I... I have to get stronger.
俺は… 俺は
強ならなければならないんだ!
I didn't ask to study under you just to hear jokes!
そんな冗談を聞ために
アナタのもとに来たのでは
断じてない ! 一
Master Saitama, your power is clearly greater
than anything you'd get from just training your body.
サイタマ先生の強さは一
明ら力ヽに体を鍛えた程度の
ものではない!
That's right, I want to know your—
ジ一ナス
そうだ 俺はお前の…>
その秘密を知り たいので萱‥
We want to know your true secret!
Genos...
サイ夕マジ工ノス
んなこと言われ亡も
他に何もね一ぞ
You may not believe me,
but that's really all I did.
阿修羅力ブ 卜 そ一力`い
Oh yeah?
おい 阿イー多羅力ブ`卜!?
No! Carnage Kabuto!
If you don't wanna tell us your secret, so be it.
阿修羅カブ 卜
秘密を教える気がねえってんなら一
構わねえぜえ…
よせ また暴走萱るつも り 力`!?
Stop! You'll go on another rampage!
I bet you aren't stronger than me anyway!
どうせ俺よか強はねえんだ‥
But, since you pissed me off,
阿修羅力ブ卜 ただし一
む力`ついた力`ら 亡めえは…一
I'm gonna annihilate you.
なぶり殺萱一
CARNAGE
MODE
Carnage Mode!
CARNAGE
MODE
阿修羅モ一 ド〕 !
CARNAGE
MODE
When I get like this I lose
control for a whole week
こうなると
もう丸ー 週間は理性が飛んで
and my lust for death
cannot be quelled!
闘争本能が静まることはない ! 一
After I kill you, I'll head into town and
go on a killing rampage until next Saturday!
お前を殺したあとは
町へ降り亡一
来週の土曜まで
大量殺戮が止まらねえぜ ! 一
さつり<
If you are indeed a strong hero,
then try and stop me!
強いヒ一口一だつたら
俺を止めてみろ!
No way... it can't be.
サイ夕マ そんな… まさ力`
フオ一‥_
Master?!
先生?
サイ夕マ マズい…一
Dammit. I may have made a horrible mistake.
俺は大変な三スを
犯したの力ヽもしれない>一
こいつの阿修羅モ一 ド・ 一
This guy's in Carnage mode...
He said he'll be on a
rampage for a whole week?
このまま丸ー週間
暴走を続けるだと!?>
Death, death, death, death, death, death,
死死死死死死死死死死死 !
death, death, death, death, death!
He'll be like this till next Saturday?
サイタマ<この調子で
来週の土曜までだと!?>一
One whole week from today...
丸ー 週間後が…一
Next Saturday...
来週の土曜・・・一
つまりは今日も
土曜つてことじゃねえかよ>一
In other words, today is Saturday too.
That means...
ということは…
It's all over.
ジ一ナス もう終わりだ一
There's no one in this world
that can stop him.
<奴を止める者は
この世に存在しない>
サイ夕マ
ということは今日が…>
That means... Today is...
Bargain day at the supermarket!
ス一パ一の特売日 じやね一力` ! _
Who the hell is this guy?
ジ一ナス 何なんだ この男は ?
I screwed up!
サイ夕マ しじつたああああ!
What is he—
ジ一ナス 何を言つている蝿
ジェノス恐らく先生は
このことを気にされている一
I'm pretty sure he's upset about this.
SATURDAY ONLY!!!
GIGANTIC SALE!
Master, the store closes at 10:00 PM.
先生 閉店は22時で萱一
We've got around four hours.
片道4 時間力`力`る道の りで萱一
力ヽなり急げば まだ間に合いま萱力ヾ
If we really hurry, we can make it.
力`な り急げば間に合うんだな ?
I'll make it if I hurry?
ジ工ノス
サイ夕マ
輪再
ご
巾・_
`ジ工ノス!
Yes!
Let's go, Genos!
Yes, Master!
ジ工ノスハイ! 先生‥
I think I'm done with evolution.
ジ一ナス
<もうやめよう こんな研究は…>一
変わるベきは一
It appears... I am the one who must change.
私なんだ…
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Yes. The on-site investigation is underway.
ヒゲ 職員 はい 今 現地で
調査していま曹が一
Yes, that's correct.
ええ そうで萱ね一
Just like the other cases, the area has been
thoroughly burnt by intense flames.
これまでと同じく 高い火力で
焼き尽<されていま萱一
恐ら<
例の若いサイボ一グと者えて一
Everything points to the young cyborg
being responsible for this.
間違いない力`と思いま萱
Yes, understood.
し力`し えげつない威力だな
Such a devastating amount of power.
Yeah...
メガネ職員 ああ…
Next
Time
The
Modern
Ninja
阿修羅カブ卜
よお~ 阿修羅力ブ卜だ一
Yo, this is Carnage Kabuto.
In Japanese my name is "Ashura Kabuto,"
俺の名前の 阿修羅 つ 亡のは一
written with the kanji for "shell,"
"field trip," and the sanskrit word "aum."
あうん
修学旅行 の修一
阿吽 の阿に
甲羅 の羅と害いて
阿修羅 なんだぜぇ一
Whaddaya think?
Bah, you don't give a damn!
どうだ? どうでもいいだろう ? _
Coming next on One-Punch Man
is episode four, "The Modern Ninja."
次回 ワンパンマン
第4話 『今時の忍者』 一
グフフ ようや<
あの男が出てくるようだぜ
So the guy is finally gonna show up?